

Fahad Bilal Mughal

Web Developer

Hi there! I am a Web Developer with 3+ years of experience in designing websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and WordPress and now getting a grip on ReactJs, Tailwind, and Azur. I also have hand on experience regarding MYSQL, Github, and Website Deployment. I create, update, optimize and modify websites and E-commerce Stores according to the needs of my employers and customers. I would love to join a thriving and hard-working team to pursue a new role. Thank You!

bilalmughal030@gmail.com

Dubai, United Arab Emirates

in linkedin.com/in/bilalmughal97

github.com/bilalmughal1

•• medium.com/@bilalmughal-1

+971 50 363 1621

🔞 fahadbilal.me

S live:.cid.927482544aa7acf5

🖹 stackoverflow.com/users/19581750/bilal-mughal? tab=profile

(O) instagram.com/bilalmughal.1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer **Brainz Technologies**

02/2019 - 03/2022 Islamabad, Pakistan

It is an Islamabad-based IT solutions company, providing services to National and international clients.

Frontend Developer/WordPress Developer

• I was responsible for designing, creating, updating, and testing dynamic websites and WordPress E-Commerce Stores.

Contact: Abdul Rehman - info@brainztechnologies.com

Teacher

Science Locus School

05/2017 - 06/2018 Gujranwala, Pakistan High School

English/Urdu/Social Studies Teacher

 2017 Best Teacher Award, Cherished Among Students, Likeable among Fellow Teachers / English Teacher, Urdu Teacher

Contact: Professor Asif - +92 300 6475963

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Domotica (11/2021 - 04/2022)

 Domotica is a web and app-based home automation system. It contains an entire system dedicated to you and your home. It is controlled by a central hub that is contacted to your home Wi-Fi network and all the devices that you want to control by web app or mobile app. It is easy to control and manage, It is designed to ease the life of the user and to fulfil its main purpose "Energy Saving.

EDUCATION

Master's In Computer Science(Mcs)

The Superior University Lahore

11/2020 - 04/2022

Courses

OPP, DLD, SE, AI, TOA, OS, DAA

Associate Degree Program(ADP)

University Of Central Punjab

11/2018 - 08/2020

Courses

 C++, OPP, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT,

Lahore, Pakistan

Lahore, Pakistan

LANGUAGES

Enalishh

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Punjabi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Coding Writing Gaming Movies Cricket **Fitness** Music